anywhere on your body.
‎涂漂白剂
-Go to your GP. -Excuse me. Otto.
‎-去看全科医生吧 ‎-打扰一下 奥托
Can one get chlamydia of the eye?
‎眼睛会感染衣原体病吗
Okay, it's Otis,
‎好吧 我叫奥蒂斯
and if infected genital fluids got into your eye, then, yes,
‎如果受感染的性器官体液 ‎流入眼中 就会感染
you can have chlamydia of the eye.
‎眼睛会感染衣原体病
But I've never had sex.
‎但我从没做过爱
It's probably conjunctivitis,
‎可能是结膜炎
‎但我不会再提供建议 ‎去看医生吧 拜托
but I'm not giving advice anymore, so go to your doctor, please.
-Uh, you have to help them. -Why, it's...
‎-你得帮助他们 ‎-怎么 这…
-It's not the same without Maeve. -Why? Her job is so easy.
‎-没有梅芙根本不行 ‎-怎么 她的工作很简单
‎就是负责预约和收钱 我帮你干吧
It's just booking appointments and taking money. I'll do it for you.
I got a B plus in business studies last year.
‎去年的商务学我考了B加
‎-你从来没学过商务学 ‎-这跟此事无关
-You never did business studies. -That's irrelevant.